Seven men with one thing in common...
Uncommon Valor is a drama, war, action film directed by Ted Kotcheff.
A group of Vietnam War veterans re-unite to rescue one of their own
left behind and taken prisoner by the Vietnamese.
Col. Cal Rhodes, played by Gene Hackman.
Wilkes, played by Fred Ward.
MacGregor, played by Robert Stack.
Kevin Scott, played by Patrick Swayze.
Johnson, played by Harold Sylvester.
Sailor, played by Randall "Tex" Cobb.
Uncommon Valor is a 1983 American action war film directed by Ted Kotcheff and starring Gene Hackman, Fred Ward,
Reb Brown, Randall "Tex" Cobb, Robert Stack, Patrick Swayze, Harold Sylvester and Tim Thomerson.
Hackman plays a former U.S.
Marine colonel, who puts together a rag-tag team to rescue his son, who he
believes is among those still held in Laos after the Vietnam War.
The film was released on December 16, 1983, and
received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, vietnam veteran, vietnam,
post-traumatic stress disorder (ptsd), war veteran.
The tone is emotional.